## Celia Diller

525 East 11th St. SE • Rome, GA 30161 crdill16@stlawu.edu • (706) 512 - 5489 www.linkedin.com/in/celia-diller- 0256a0166

### **SUMMARY**

I am a UI/UX Design Student experienced in user testing and product creating. I excel in customer service with a history of working in varied industries. I am progressive in investigating the integration of multiple disciplines to create an improved realm of problem-solving in the workplace.

### **EDUCATION**

## UI Design Certification with specialization In Frontend Development for Design SKILLS:

March 2021- December 2021

TOOLS:

User Flow User Testing

Visual Design

Wireframes

Brand Building

- Adobe XD
- Procreate
- Figma
- Marvel
- Illustrator

### Bachelor of Science in Biology and Business in the Liberal Arts

August 2016 - May 2020

St. Lawrence University - Canton, NY

Concentration: Business and Biology Credits Earned- Bachelor of Science

#### RELEVANT COURSES

### **SKILLS**

- Financial & Managerial Accounting
- Lab Animals
- Biology Cell Biology Research Methods
- Leadership and Public Relations
- Microeconomics and Macroeconomics
- Direct and Indirect Marketing Experience
- Experience in Handling Lab Animals
- 5+ Years of Customer Service Experience
- Social Media Management and Marketing
- Cell Biology Lab Experience
- Public Speaking and Communication
- Adept in Microsoft Office (Word, Excel, PWPT, Outlook)

### **EXPERIENCE**

# The Desoto Theatre - Rome, GA

September 2020 - November 2021

Social Media Marketing Assistant

- Excelled at creating visual content (Instagram posts/stories, Facebook posts, videos, and slideshows) to help increase donations for the renovations of the theatre.
- Created and implemented a Facebook Strategy to help boost ticket sales for events.
- Re-organizing newspaper clippings and photos historically to allow Board members to have easy access in the future.
- Presented verbal and visual presentations during various Board/Donor meetings to increase funds for renovations.

## Sunflour Community Bakery - Rome, GA

June 2019 - Present

Business Developmental Internship

- Undertook a direct marketing role by promoting the company through farmers markets and direct sales in the bakery.
- Excelled at an indirect marketing role by designing an aesthetically attractive website and social media presence in the
- Mastered the point of sale system (Clover) by handling set up of the system, maintaining online orders, adding/editing inventory, adding new employees and editing rewards systems for consumers.
- Created themes and ideas to further customer interest in the small business community.
- Greeted guests, addressed in-house issues, and managed over the phone transactions.

## Barista/ Sales Associate - Brewer Bookstore in Canton, NY

August 2016 - March 2020

Caribou Coffee

- Obtained advance knowledge about coffee/tea blends and different coffee drinks.
- Contributed past my job role by contributing new product ideas, organizational support and analytical skills to the bookstore team.

- Innovated new coffee drinks and prepared the pastry case in a aesthetically pleasing way.
- Trained new student workers the point of sale system and taught the products we provide in the cafe.
- Obtained great multitasking skills in a high fast-paced environment and experience in keeping consumers happy and safe.